
City Street Skyboxes Vol. 1 documentation

Skyboxes in _MW Skybox Vol. 02/MAT scene folder - drag and drop a skybox to your scene background.
Eventually adjust settings - Exposure, Rotation 
Map setting:
(maps in _MW Skybox Vol. 02/ MAPS scene folder)
Maps are set up for maximum resolution (8k) decrease if necessary.
Compression: Normal Quality for day/dawn seems sufficient,
High Quality for night skyboxes to avoid gamut issues.
Generate Mip Maps: uncheck to avoid seams in the background texture.
